(Bernadette:)So even though
he's happy for me,
(Bernadette:)it's just a little tough on him.
(Penny:)Uh-oh.
What?
(Raj:)Well,
(Penny:)if I do well in sales,
(Penny:)I could end up making a
lot more money than you.
(Leonard:)Not a problem.
I grew up with a mother
(Leonard:)who emasculated
my father financially
(Leonard:)and in every other aspect
of his life, so...
(Leonard:)...really, it's what I think
love looks like.
(Bernadette:)I'll be right back.
I'm gonna go check on him.
(Penny:)Maybe it's a good
thing we came here.
(Penny:)It's like a lesson
in what not to do.
Yeah.
(Leonard:)I don't want something dumb
like money to come between us.
(Penny:)It won't. Let's just promise
to figure this kind of stuff out
(Penny:)before we get married.
WOLOWITZ:
Why are you
being so bossy?!
BERNADETTE:
Why are you
being a baby?
WOLOWITZ:
I'm not a baby!
I'm a grown man,
(Howard(off):)and I made the bed.
Now where's my star?
(Leonard:)Should we go?
Hang on.
(Penny:)I want to see if
he gets the star.
(Raj:)Oh, this heat is brutal.
(Sheldon:)As someone from the tropical
subcontinent of India,